multilingualbooks.com 2008-12-28

# Privacy Statement

---  
|  **Free Shipping On All Orders Over $100! US/CDN Only.**    
**Business/Sales: 206-708-6948 | 206-384-3728**    

The Internet Language Company (ILC) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website (www.multilingualbooks.com). 

## Information Collection and Use

The Internet Language Company is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to others. We will not share this information with others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The Internet Language Company collects information from our users at several different points on this website. 

## Order Form

We request information from our users on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. A telephone number is required for orders outside the United States. Order information, including credit card numbers, is transmitted to the Internet Language Company via secure, encrypted (SSL) connections. 

## Surveys and Polls

Multilingual Books offers users the option of participating in online surveys and polls. Surveys and polls help us improve our site by offering services, information, and products that are more relevant to our users. Our surveys and polls do not collect any information which may be used to personally identify a participant. 

## InstantService Chat

Multilingual Books offers a special type of online communication called InstantService. InstantService on Multilingual Books allows users to correspond with Internet Language Company staff in real time by typing messages back and forth. InstantService sessions take place over secure, encrypted (SSH) connections; only the user and Internet Language Company staff can read or participate in the session. When a user logs in to Multilingual Books InstantService, they must enter their name, email address, and phone number. This information is stored along with a log of the entire conversation on a secure server and is only accessible to the Internet Language Company. This information is not shared outside the Internet Language Company, and is only used to better service our customers. Multilingual Books InstantService users will not be added to our mailing list unless they explicitly ask to be subscribed. 

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is not stored in connection with any personally identifiable information. Multilingual Books InstantService chat sessions are kept in a log file; for more information, see the above section called “InstantService Chat”. 

## Sharing

We share aggregated statistical information (such as traffic figures) with our partners and advertisers. This data is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside credit card processing company to bill our customers. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that the Internet Language Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such Web sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects personally identifiable information. If you have a comment or complaint to make about a site that we link to, please email **[sales@multilingualbooks.com](mailto:sales@multilingualbooks.com)**. 

## Security

We take every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via this web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number), that information is encrypted and protected with industry-standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption. Credit card numbers collected on this web site transmitted to the Internet Language Company using secure, encrypted (SSL) email. Ordering online from Multilingual Books is secure and safe. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. Employees of the Internet Language Company are required to sign a contract which specifies that they will follow our strict security and privacy policies. All of our internal computer systems and servers are password protected, and all paper documents containing sensitive information are shredded when they are no longer in use. 

We feel that Multilingual Books is one of the safest places to shop on the web. If you have any questions about the security at our web site, send an email to **[sales@multilingualbooks.com](mailto:sales@multilingualbooks.com)**. 

## Choice / Opt-In / Opt-Out

Our site provides customers with the opportunity to subscribe to our monthly email newsletter by entering their email address into a box on the home page . If a customer wishes to discontinue their subscription to the newsletter, they can send an email to [**remove@multilingualbooks.com**](mailto:remove@multilingualbooks.com). Information on how to unsubscribe is included on every Internet Language Company newsletter. 

## Correct / Update

Users of Multilingual Books may change or modify information previously collected on this site by sending an email to **[sales@multilingualbooks.com](mailto:sales@multilingualbooks.com)**. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

**Multilingual Books  
1309 NE Ravenna Boulevard  
Seattle, WA 98105  
**

**E-mail:** **[sales@multilingualbooks.com](mailto:sales@multilingualbooks.com)**

* * *

**Multilingual Books**  
**11515 NE 26th Ave Suite 201**  
**Seattle, WA 98125** |  **Business/Sales: 206-708-6948 | 206-384-3728**    
**Fax: 206-400-1156**  
---|---  
**Copyright © 1996-2009 Multilingual Books**
